<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Services on Gill&#39;s Crane Services</title>
    <link>https://gillscraneservices.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Services on Gill&#39;s Crane Services</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2024 14:24:05 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://gillscraneservices.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>More Information Request Pile Driving</title>
      <link>https://gillscraneservices.com/more-information-request-pile-driving/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2024 14:24:05 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://gillscraneservices.com/more-information-request-pile-driving/</guid>
      <description>What question do you have on our Pile Driving services? We have the capability to work both from land and barge, allowing us to drive piles of various lengths and types. Whether your project requires driving timber piles, pipe piles, concrete piles, H piles, or sheet piles, we have the expertise and equipment to handle it efficiently and effectively. Our team can drive piles up to 100 feet in length and 24 inches in diameter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More Information Request Marine Construction Service</title>
      <link>https://gillscraneservices.com/more-information-request-marine-construction-service/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2024 14:23:40 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://gillscraneservices.com/more-information-request-marine-construction-service/</guid>
      <description>Gill’s Crane Services is a leader in marine construction within the saltwater environments of Louisiana and Mississippi. Our extensive experience and specialized skills enable us to handle a variety of projects in these challenging conditions. We understand the unique requirements of saltwater construction, ensuring every project is built to withstand the harsh marine environment. In addition to new construction, we offer comprehensive repair services for existing marine structures. Whether it&#39;s storm damage or general wear and tear, our team can restore your docks, piers, and boathouses to their original condition.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More Information Request Bulkheads</title>
      <link>https://gillscraneservices.com/more-information-request-bulkheads/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2024 14:23:10 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://gillscraneservices.com/more-information-request-bulkheads/</guid>
      <description>Are you building or repairing a marine bulkhead? Bulkhead Considerations for Louisiana and Mississippi Saltwater Environments: Corrosion Resistance: The high salinity in these coastal and marshy areas accelerates the corrosion of metal components. Using materials like vinyl, fiberglass, treated lumber and treated steel with protective coatings is crucial. Marine Life: Marine borers and other organisms can deteriorate wooden components, so pressure-treated or composite materials are preferred. Wave and Tidal Forces: Bulkheads are designed to withstand the dynamic forces of waves and tides, which are significant in these regions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More Information Request Boat Houses</title>
      <link>https://gillscraneservices.com/more-information-request-boat-houses/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2024 14:22:58 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://gillscraneservices.com/more-information-request-boat-houses/</guid>
      <description>Are you looking to repair or build a new boat house? Gill’s Crane Services is the premier boathouse builder on the coasts of Louisiana and Mississippi. With years of experience, we specialize in constructing top-notch boathouses designed to function properly in the waterfront environment. Our boathouses not only protect your boat from the weather but also provide a great place to stay. Many of our projects become cherished man caves and family party rooms.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More Information Request Boat Launch Repair &amp; Construction</title>
      <link>https://gillscraneservices.com/more-information-request-boat-launch-building/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2024 14:22:58 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://gillscraneservices.com/more-information-request-boat-launch-building/</guid>
      <description>Are you looking to repair or build a new boat launch? Building a boat launch in the bayous, canals, lakes, and rivers of coastal Louisiana and Mississippi often involves driving piles and creating a sturdy deck for easy launching and recovery of boats. Homeowners and municipalities alike turn to Gill’s Crane Services because we are licensed, insured, and bondable for even the most complex marine construction projects. Having sufficient ramp length to launch a boat is a critical factor in constructing a reliable boat launch.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More Information Request Docks</title>
      <link>https://gillscraneservices.com/more-information-request-docks/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2024 14:22:48 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://gillscraneservices.com/more-information-request-docks/</guid>
      <description>Boat Dock Builder for Slidell &amp; New Orleans Area Find out the reasons to choose a Gill’s Crane to build your boat dock. A boat dock is an important part of any water-front construction project in which you hope to use or type of marine vessels and boats. Getting your project off the ground right is important. A well-constructed dock can last for years, but a poorly constructed dock or bulkhead system can begin failing quickly.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bulkhead Builder and Repair</title>
      <link>https://gillscraneservices.com/services/bulkhead-builder-and-repair/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 22:01:59 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://gillscraneservices.com/services/bulkhead-builder-and-repair/</guid>
      <description>Bulkhead building and repair in south Louisiana and Mississippi Gill’s Crane is the premier waterfront contractor in South Louisiana and Coastal Mississippi for building and repairing bulkheads.&#xA;A bulkhead is the sheeting and piling system designed to reduce erosion and the impacts water on a piece of property. Bulkheads can be damaged by storms or need repair after sometime. Gill’s Crane has been building and repairing bulkheads since 1973. We will be glad to provide and estimate and get your project under control and off to the right start.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pile Driving</title>
      <link>https://gillscraneservices.com/services/pile-driving/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 22:00:03 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://gillscraneservices.com/services/pile-driving/</guid>
      <description>Pile Driver in New Orleans Area Need pilings or bulkead pilings driven? </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boat House Builder</title>
      <link>https://gillscraneservices.com/services/boat-house-builder/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 21:48:59 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://gillscraneservices.com/services/boat-house-builder/</guid>
      <description>Gill’s Crane Services works all over the Louisiana and Mississippi coastlines. We specialize in marine construction services and are located in Slidell, Louisiana since 1973. Need a reliable marine contractor in one of the communities below? Give us a call or fill out a request information form. Slidell Slidell, located in St. Tammany Parish, offers stunning waterfront views of Lake Pontchartrain. The area&#39;s waterfront make for lots of docks, boat houses, marinas and boat launches.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Waveland</title>
      <link>https://gillscraneservices.com/market/waveland/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 20:55:49 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://gillscraneservices.com/market/waveland/</guid>
      <description>Waveland, Mississippi Gill’s Crane Services works all over the Louisiana and Mississippi coastlines. We specialize in marine construction services and are located in Slidell, Louisiana since 1973. Need a reliable marine contractor in one of the communities below? Give us a call or fill out a request information form. Slidell Slidell, located in St. Tammany Parish, offers stunning waterfront views of Lake Pontchartrain. The area&#39;s waterfront make for lots of docks, boat houses, marinas and boat launches.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Slidell</title>
      <link>https://gillscraneservices.com/market/slidell/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 20:25:25 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://gillscraneservices.com/market/slidell/</guid>
      <description>Slidell, Louisiana Gill’s Crane Services works all over the Louisiana and Mississippi coastlines. We specialize in marine construction services and are located in Slidell, Louisiana since 1973. Need a reliable marine contractor in one of the communities below? Give us a call or fill out a request information form. Slidell Slidell, located in St. Tammany Parish, offers stunning waterfront views of Lake Pontchartrain. The area&#39;s waterfront make for lots of docks, boat houses, marinas and boat launches.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Work Areas</title>
      <link>https://gillscraneservices.com/work-areas/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 20:16:33 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://gillscraneservices.com/work-areas/</guid>
      <description>Gill&amp;rsquo;s Crane Service work areas Gill’s Crane Services works all over the Louisiana and Mississippi coastlines. We specialize in marine construction services and are located in Slidell, Louisiana since 1973. Need a reliable marine contractor in one of the communities below? Give us a call or fill out a request information form. Slidell Slidell, located in St. Tammany Parish, offers stunning waterfront views of Lake Pontchartrain. The area&#39;s waterfront make for lots of docks, boat houses, marinas and boat launches.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://gillscraneservices.com/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 20:10:19 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://gillscraneservices.com/contact/</guid>
      <description> Contact Gill&#39;s Crane Services Get Started On Your Marine Construction Project Today! Phone: 504-662-5530 Fax: 985-781-7569 Office Contacts Email Us: Corporate Accountant Allison@gillscrane.com&#xA;Owners Brett@gillscrane.com&#xA;Ryan@gillscrane.com Address: 116 Marlin Dr. Slidell, LA 70461 Fill out my online form. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>404</title>
      <link>https://gillscraneservices.com/404/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://gillscraneservices.com/404/</guid>
      <description> Page not found - 404 Sorry we couldn&#39;t find your page, we were out driving piles on this bulkhead. Give us a call to discuss your questions: (504) 662-5530 </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://gillscraneservices.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://gillscraneservices.com/about/</guid>
      <description>About Gill&#39;s Crane Services Gill’s Crane Service, Inc. was started in 1973 by the entrepreneurial spirit of Gill J. Audibert. Mr. Audibert, a native of New Orleans, had been working for Boh Brothers, LLC since the age of fifteen. Like his older brothers before him, Mr. Audibert took a position there as a laborer and worked his way up to the operator.&#xA;After working there for over ten years, Mr.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Get Estimate</title>
      <link>https://gillscraneservices.com/request-an-estimate/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://gillscraneservices.com/request-an-estimate/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
